rubios.com 2019-07-16

# Privacy | Rubio's

**RECENT PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES**

We've recently made changes to our privacy policy. These changes are: 

1\. We have clarified that we collect and use cookies when you navigate and browse our website unless you disable them in your browser. 

2\. We have clarified that we may use your personal information for marketing purposes and may share your personal information with our service providers who support our business and who are bound to keep your information confidential and only use it for the purposes for which we disclose it to them. We will not share your information with third parties or for purposes other than as described in our privacy policy.

 **Our Commitment to Privacy**

At rubios.com, our foremost consideration is to ensure that our visitors have a safe and secure online experience with us. We consider the information you choose to share with us personal and confidential and we are extremely committed to protecting your privacy. Rubio's is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. We believe that it is important that you understand how we treat the information that we receive from you. We created this Website Privacy Policy in order to ensure the confidence of visitors to this Website, and to demonstrate our commitment to fair practices and the protection of privacy. This Privacy Policy has been developed with the recognition that Internet technologies are rapidly evolving, and that underlying business models still may not be established or mature. Accordingly, this Privacy Policy is subject to change at Rubio's sole and unilateral discretion, at any time with or without advance notice. Any such changes will be posted on this Site. Any such change, update or modification will be effective immediately upon its posting on this Site.

 **VeriSign**

VeriSign is the leading provider of critical infrastructure services that make the Internet and telecommunication networks more reliable, reliable and secure. VeriSign's technology helps hundreds of thousands of businesses and millions of consumers connect, communicate, and transact with confidence. Our website is certified as a licensee of the VeriSign Secure Site Program.

 **Information We Collect**

 **Traffic Data**

We collect two types of information: Traffic Data and Personal Information. We automatically track and collect the following information when you visit our Site: your (i) IP address; (ii) domain server; (iii) type of computer; and (iv) type of web browser (collectively, "Traffic Data"). Traffic Data is anonymous information that does not personally identify you but is helpful for marketing purposes or for improving your experience on the Site. For example, we use this information for statistical purposes, such as measuring the average time spent on the Site and the pages viewed on the Site.

 **Cookies**

We share our information with contractors, service providers, and other third parties that we use to support our business and who are bound by contractual obligations to keep your information confidential and to only use it for the purposes for which we disclose it to them.

As you navigate through and interact with our site, we may use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions, and patterns, including through the use of cookies. A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our website. You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. However, if you do not consent to our use of cookies or select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our sites. You can find more information about cookies at [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

 **Personal Information**

At the time you subscribe to the e-club (Rubio's Beach Club), make a gift card purchase, order online, book a fundraiser, or agree to participate in a contest/promotion, we collect and store the following types of information:

Name  
Address  
E-mail address  
Telephone number  
Credit/Debit Card Information - only in encrypted form on secure servers

We need this information to provide you not only with the information that you've requested but also to let you know about additional services which you might want. We may also use this information to customize your experience using our website.

If you order a gift card and want it to be sent directly to the recipient, we will also ask you to submit information about someone other than you. In such situations, we will ask only for the recipient's name, address, telephone number and e-mail address.

 **Surveys and Contests**

From time-to-time, Rubio's will request additional information from customers through surveys, sweepstakes or other contests. Participation in these are strictly voluntary and the user has the choice of whether or not to disclose this information. In addition, all customers will always be provided with an opportunity to opt out of receiving such future e-mails. Information requested may include contact and demographic information. In addition, we may automatically gather general statistical information about our website and visitors, such as IP addresses, browsers, pages viewed, number of visitors, gift cards purchased, etc., but in doing so we do not reference you by individual name, e-mail address, home address, or telephone number. We use this data in the aggregate to determine how much our customers use parts of our site so we can improve the customer experience on our site. We may provide this statistical information to third parties, but when we do so we do not provide personally identifying information without your permission.

 **How We Use the Information**

Our goal is to provide you with a site that best meets your needs, wants and interests. Therefore, we primarily use the information we've collected to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to statistically analyze site usage, to improve our content and product offerings and to customize our site's content, layout, and services.

The information that we collect is used by us to contact consumers for marketing purposes. We do not share, sell, or otherwise disclose your information for purposes other than those outlined in this privacy notice. 

If you placed a gift card order or ordered online, we use your personal information to fulfill your order.

 **Security**

Rubio's takes your online privacy very seriously. As such, we employ policies and procedures meant to prevent others from illegal and/or unauthorized access to the personal information you provide to us.

Access to your information is controlled by strict internal procedures.

When you register as a visitor to the site, you will choose a user identification name and a password. You are solely responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your password and user ID. As such, you are responsible for any and all activities that occur within your account, including, but not limited to, properly exiting a session on the site. Additionally, you agree to notify us immediately of any unauthorized use of your password, account, or any other breach of security.

 **Children Under 13**

We do not knowingly collect or use personal information from children under 13 without the proper consent from their parents. However, in the case a child has provided us with personal information without parental or guardian consent, the parent or guardian should contact us immediately to remove their information.

For more information about the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), visit the FTC website: [www.ftc.gov](http://www.ftc.gov/).

 **Policy Updates**

The practices, policies, and procedures described in this statement are subject to change. Any such changes will be communicated through our website. Information collected before changes are made will be secured according to the previous Privacy Policy. The practices and policies in this disclosure replace all previous notices or statements with respect to the same subject matter.

 **Understanding and Consent**  
By using our website, you agree to the collection and use of this information in the manner described above.

 **How to Reach Rubio's**

To update, correct or delete your personal information, you can contact us at:

Rubio's Restaurants, Inc.  
2200 Faraday Ave, Suite 250  
Carlsbad, CA 92008

You may reach us by telephone, toll-free at 1-800-354-4199.
